Privacy Policy
==============

The administration of the site AN1.com (hereinafter the Site) respects the rights of visitors to the Site. We unconditionally recognize the importance of confidentiality of personal information of our Site visitors. This page contains information about what information we receive and collect when you use the Site. We hope you can use this information to make informed decisions about the personal information you provide us.  
  
This Privacy Policy applies only to the Site and the information collected by and through the Site. It does not apply to any other site and it does not apply to any third party websites from which links may be made to the Site.  
  
**Collection of Information**  
When you visit the Site, we measure your ISP's domain name and country (for example, "aol.com") and selected page conversions (referred to as "clickstream activity").  
  
The information we receive on the Site may be used to facilitate your use of the Site, including, but not limited to:  
\- Organizing the Site in the most user-friendly manner possible.  
  
The Site only collects personal information that you provide voluntarily when you visit or register on the Site. Personal information includes information that identifies you as a specific individual, such as your name or email address. While you can browse the content of the Site without having to register, you will need to register in order to use certain features, such as leaving a comment on an article.  
  
The Site uses "cookies" for statistical reporting. A "cookie" is a small amount of data sent by a website, which your computer's browser stores on your computer's hard drive. Cookies" contain information that may be needed by the Site, to store your browsing preferences and statistical information about the Site, i.e. which pages you have visited, what you have downloaded, the domain name of your Internet service provider and the country of the visitor, and the addresses of third party websites from which you linked to the Site and beyond. However, all of this information has nothing to do with you as an individual. "Cookies" do not record your e-mail address or any personal information about you. Also, this technology is used on the Site by Yandex's installed counter.  
  
In addition, we use standard web server logs to count the number of visitors and to estimate the technical capabilities of our Site. We use this information to determine how many people visit the Site and to organize pages in the most user-friendly manner, to ensure that the Site matches the browsers used, and to make the content of our pages as useful to our visitors as possible. We record information on the movements on the Site, but not about individual visitors to the Site, so that no specific information about you personally will not be saved or used by the Site Administration without your consent  
  
To view content without cookies, you may set your browser to not accept cookies or to notify you when a cookie is being sent (these cookies are different, so we suggest that you check the "Help" section to see how to change your cookie settings).  
  
**Sharing information**  
We will not sell or rent your personal information to any third party under any circumstances. We also do not disclose your personal information, except as required by U.S. law.  
  
Site Administration has a partnership with Google, which places advertising materials and advertisements (including, but not limited to, text hyperlinks) on pages of this site on a reimbursable basis. Within the framework of this cooperation the Administration of this site brings to the attention of all interested parties the following information:  
1\. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to display ads on the Site;  
2\. DoubleClick DART ad product cookies are used by Google in ads displayed on the Site as a member of the AdSense program for content.  
3\. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to collect and use information about visitors to the Site (other than your name, address, email address or telephone number), about your visits to the Site and other websites in order to provide the most relevant ads for products and services.  
4\. Google follows its own privacy policy when collecting this information;  
5\. Users of the Site may opt-out of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google Ads Privacy Policy and the Google Affiliate Sites Network](https://an1.com/engine/go.php?url=aHR0cHM6Ly9wb2xpY2llcy5nb29nbGUuY29tL3RlY2hub2xvZ2llcy9hZHM%3D).  
  
**Disclaimer**  
Please be aware that the transmission of personally identifiable information when you visit third-party sites, including affiliate websites, even if the website contains a link to the Site or if the Site contains a link to such websites, is not governed by this policy. This Site is not responsible for the practices of other web sites. The process of collecting and transmitting personal information when you visit these websites is governed by the "Protection of Personal Information" or similar document located on the websites of these companies.

[](https://an1.com/)2015—2024. © AN1.COMGames, programs for android

Search
